Guide to the Travel brochure and map collection, [19--].
Travel brochure and map collection, [19--]
- Description: City/ Region, State
  - Map: Winchester, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Historic Sites: Winchester, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Victory Center: Yorktown, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Bridge-Tunnel Map: Chesapeake Bay-Follow The Gulls!, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Bridge-Tunnel Map: Chesapeake Bay, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Booklet: William & Mary College, Virginia, Williamsburg (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Esso Map: Hampton Roads, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - American Map: Hampton-Norfolk Map, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Texaco Map: Tidewater, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Map: Entire, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - National Park Concessions Map: Blue Ridge Parkway, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - U. S. Dept. of the Interior Map: Blue Ridge Parkway, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Map: Lower Peninsula, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Covered Bridges: Entire, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Wineries: Entire, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Civil War Sites: Entire, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Dept. of Highways Map and guide: Entire, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Map: Partial, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - State Historical Markers: Entire, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Visitor's Guide: Charlottesville, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Monticello: Charlottesville, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - History: Chesterfield County, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Points of Interest: Fredericksburg, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Historic sites: Fredericksburg, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - History: Fort Eustis, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 1940, 1950, 1955: Garden Week, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Map: Harrisonburg, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Doe Run: Groundhog Mtn., Virginia (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Geological survey: York-James Peninsula, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Navigation Co.: James River Tours, Virginia (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Tidewater: Colonial Williamsburg, Virginia, Williamsburg (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Postcards leaflet: Colonial Williamsburg, Virginia, Williamsburg (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Postcard: Colonial Williamsburg, Virginia, Williamsburg (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Handbook for Exhibition Buildings, 1937 (2 copies): Colonial Williamsburg, Virginia, Williamsburg (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 1931 Restoration: Colonial Williamsburg, Virginia, Williamsburg (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Restoration: Colonial Williamsburg, Virginia, Williamsburg (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Handbook for Exhibition Buildings, 1941: Colonial Williamsburg, Virginia, Williamsburg (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Raleigh Tavern: Colonial Williamsburg, Virginia, Williamsburg (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Travis House: Colonial Williamsburg, Virginia, Williamsburg (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Official guidebook & map: Colonial Williamsburg, Virginia, Williamsburg (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Map: Colonial Williamsburg, Virginia, Williamsburg (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Colonial National Monument: Colonial Williamsburg, Virginia, Williamsburg (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Leaflets (2): Birthplace of the Nation, Virginia, Jamestown (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Booklet, 1907: Jamestown Exposition, Virginia, Jamestown (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - National Park Service Handbook: The Town Site and Its Story, Virginia, Jamestown (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Leaflet: Jamestown Island Historical Park, Virginia, Jamestown (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Booklet: Glassmaking, Virginia, Jamestown (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Booklet: Jamestown Story, Virginia, Jamestown (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Postcards: Postcard leaflet, Virginia, Mt. Vernon (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Postcards: Loose Postcards (6), Virginia, Mt. Vernon (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 1940 edition: Handbook, 1940, Virginia, Mt. Vernon (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 1928 edition: Illustrated Handbook, Virginia, Mt. Vernon (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 1912 edition: Illustrated Handbook, Virginia, Mt. Vernon (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Mount Vernon/An Illustrated Handbook, Virginia, Mt. Vernon (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 1948 edition: Handbook, Virginia, Mt. Vernon (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Leaflets (2): Map and Guide, Virginia, Mt. Vernon (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Booklet: Washington's Home and the Story, Virginia, Mt. Vernon (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 1963 edition: Capitol Guide, Virginia, Richmond (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Postcard leaflets (2): Souvenirs of Richmond, Virginia, Richmond (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - : St. John P.E. Church, Virginia, Richmond (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - 1937: Historic Tour, Virginia, Richmond (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - 1927 edition: Pocket Directory & Guide, Virginia, Richmond (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Esso area map: Richmond-Petersburg, Virginia, Richmond (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Exxon area map: Richmond-Petersburg, Virginia, Richmond (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Handbook, 1920: Old Yorktown & Its History, Virginia, Yorktown (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - National Park Service booklet: Climax of the Revolution, Virginia, Yorktown (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Senate document #322: Journal of the Siege at York-Town, Virginia, Yorktown (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - National Park Service handbook: Yorktown and the Siege of 1781, Virginia, Yorktown (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Leaflet: Battlefield, Virginia, Yorktown (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Guide and map: 1938, 1940, 1941 (2): Colonial National Historical Park, Virginia, Yorktown (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Leaflet: Victory Center, Virginia, Yorktown (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Battlefield guide: Moore House, Virginia, Yorktown (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Leaflet: Town of York self-guided tour, Virginia, Yorktown (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Map: Yorktown Battlefield, Virginia, Yorktown (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Esso: Map + Visitor's Guide, Washington DC (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Exxon: Map + Visitor's Guide, Washington DC (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - AAA Map: Street + Visitor's Guide, Washington DC (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Shaw's Guide: Capitol Hill, Washington DC (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - AAA Map: Street map, Washington DC (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Esso Maps (2): Pictorial guide, Washington DC (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Esso Map: Pictorial road map, Washington DC (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - AAA Map: DC & adjacent areas, Washington DC (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Guide map: Capital Transit Street Car and Bus Lines, Washington DC (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Declaration of Independence: Entire, Washington DC (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Guide: Washington Cathedral, Washington DC (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Glad: Guide to the Presidents [Washington, DC] (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - The White House [Washington, DC] (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - The United States Marine Corps War Memorial [Washington, DC] (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Washington Monument, Washington, DC (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Leaflet: Dry Falls, Washington State (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Steamboat trip: Lake Chelan, Washington State (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - National Parks leaflet: Ross Lake + Lake Chelan, Washington State (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Power Plant: Rock Island, Washington State (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Geology: Grand Coulee, Washington State (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - National Park Guide 1936: Mount Rainier, Washington State (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Guide 1937: Mt. Rainier, Washington State (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - National Park guide 1965: Mount Rainier, Washington State (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Park Guide 1971: Mount Rainier, Washington State (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Park Guide 1978: Mount Rainier, Washington State (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Map and guide: North Cascades Highway, Washington State (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Guide + Map: Olympic National Park, Washington State (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Brochure: Soap Lake, Washington State (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Clipping: Logging contest, Washington State (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Clipping: Fire fighting, Washington State (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Leaflet: Beckley Coal Mine, West Virginia (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Park Guide: New River Gorge, West Virginia (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Map: Beckley, West Virginia (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - AAA Map: Western States and Provinces, Western U. S. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Enco map: Route guide, Western U. S. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Exxon map: Highway system, Western U. S. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Socony-Vacuum Oil Company, Inc.: Interstate travel guide, Western U. S. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Book: Superior, Wisconsin (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - The Enchanted Summer-Land (pamphlet): Entire, Wisconsin (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Standard Map: Entire, Wisconsin (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Citgo map: Milwaukee, Wisconsin (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Enco Map: Milwaukee, Wisconsin (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Yosemite Lodging: Yellowstone, Wyoming (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Buffalo Bill Center: Yellowstone, Wyoming (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Devil's Tower: Yellowstone, Wyoming (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Highway Map: Yellowstone, Wyoming (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Map: Yellowstone, Wyoming (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Map and Guide: Yellowstone, Wyoming (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Map and Guide: Yellowstone, Wyoming (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - National Park centennial: Yellowstone, Wyoming (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Park Guide: Yellowstone, Wyoming (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Park History: Yellowstone, Wyoming (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Jackson Hole Birds: Yellowstone, Wyoming (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Fountain Paint Pot Nature Trail: Yellowstone, Wyoming (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Mud Volcano Trail: Yellowstone, Wyoming (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Cooke City Highway: Yellowstone, Wyoming (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Geological history: Yellowstone, Wyoming (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Plants: Yellowstone, Wyoming (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - N. Pacific Railway: Yellowstone, Wyoming (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - People of Africa Map: Entire, Africa (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Guide: East Africa (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Africa: Morocco Guide (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Africa: Morocco Road Map (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Africa: Tanzania Road Map (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Africa: Ethopia Map (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Road Map of East Africa (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Heritage Map of Africa (National Geographic Magazine) 1971 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Event Guide: International, Airlines (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Overture (airline magazine): U.S. Airways (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Marriott Rewards: U.S. Airlines (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - DVD rental: NA, Airlines (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Attache magazine: NA, Airlines (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Attache magazine: NA, Airlines (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Security Brief: NA, Airlines (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Brochure (2 copies): Air France, Airlines (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Brochure (2 copies): Air "Plus" France, Airlines (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Royal Dutch Flight: Netherlands, Airlines (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Unknown soldiers grave, Algiers, Algeria (photograph) 1929 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Dept. travel: Entire, Argentina (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - General Info: Entire, Bahamas (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Belarus: pamphlet on history and symbols of Belarus (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Belarus: leaflet on living and working in Gomel (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Dept. travel: Entire, Bolivia (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - General Info: Entire, Brazil (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - What is your IQ on Brazil? (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Principal products of Brazil (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Brazil at a glance (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - An outline of Brazilian history 1953 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Spoken Portuguese 1946 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - What you want to say and how to say it: Portuguese 1943 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - A pocket guide to spoken Portuguese (Brazilian) 1954 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Brazil 1952 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Some views of Brazil (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Brazilian American Survey 1953-1954 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Brazilian Magazine 1953 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Igreja de pampulha (Saint Francis of Assisi Church), Minas Gerais (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Traveler's Guide to Rio, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Lembranca do Rio de Janeiro, 10 fotografias (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Lembranca do Rio de Janeiro, 10 cartoes postaes (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Ouro verde hotel, Rio de Janeiro, registration card (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Real S.A. Transportes Aeros envelope (with routes map) (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Rio de Janeiro, 14 postcards (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Roteiro do Rio Grande do Sul (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Brasil moderno 1953 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Winnipeg Lodging: General + Parks, Canada (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Pacific Coast Tours through the Canadian Rockies: Montreal or Toronto-Vancouver, Canada (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Ontario close up: General + Parks, Canada (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - French River Lodge (envelope), Pickerel River, Ont., Canada (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Ottawa Tourist Guide (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Peggy's cove Nova scotia: General + Parks, Canada (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Lake of Bays Muskoka: General + Parks, Canada (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Algonquin Provincial Park: General + Parks, Canada (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Jasper: General + Parks, Canada (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Saskathchewan Manitoba: General + Parks, Canada (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - British Columbia Yukon Alberta: General + Parks, Canada (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Maps: Entire, Canada (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Maps: Quebec Hostels, Canada (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Maps: Entire, Canada (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Maps: Entire, Canada (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Maps: Montreal, Canada (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Maps: New Brunswick, Canada (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Maps: Quebec, Canada (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Maps: Quebec, Canada (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Maps: Entire, Canada (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Maps: Vancouver/ Victoria, Canada (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Triangle Tours: Rainier National Park, Seattle, Victoria, Vancouver, Banff; Canada (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Maps: Metropolitan Quebec, Canada (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Maps: Ontario, Canada (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Canadian National Exhibition: Toronto, Canada (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Map: Bermuda, Caribbean (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Texaco Map: Trinidad Tobago, Caribbean (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Map: West Indies, Caribbean (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Map: Entire, Caribbean (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Curacao: Antilles, Caribbean (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Curacao: Netherland Antilles, Caribbean (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - South America: Guyana, Caribbean Picture Book (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Barbados, Caribbean - Hotel (leaflet) (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Trinidad, Caribbean - Sightseeing Guide (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Jamaica, Caribbean - Road Map (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Jamaica, Caribbean - Sightseeing Guide (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Map: Netherlands West Indies, Caribbean (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Texaco Map: Haiti, Caribbean (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Map: Entire, Caribbean (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Archeological Map: Entire, Central America (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Texaco Map: Honduras, Central America (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Travel to China (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - China travel guide (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Bamboo shoot cookbook (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - How China became self-sufficient in grain 1977 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - A glance at China's economy 1974 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - China: a general survey 1979 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - An outline of Chinese history 1978 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Entomological pamphlet (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Entomological portfolio (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Currency: 1 yi jiao (3), 2 er jiao (6), 5 wu jiao (3), 1 yi yuan (4), 2 er yuan (1), 5 wu yuan (1), 10 shi yuan (1) (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Great Wall (postage stamps, four different scenes/views): 8 jiao (15), 60 jiao (5) (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Beijing (tourist map), China (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Forbidden City (panorama postcards), Beijing, China (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Forbidden City (postcards), Beijing, China (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Beijing (postcards), China (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Former imperial palaces (postcards), Beijing, China (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Summer palace I (postcards), Beijing, China (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Summer palace II (postcards), Beijing, China (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Opera program, Beijing, China (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Guide: Canton, China (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Changsha Mawangdui Hanmu, China (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Chenkiang/Chiaoshan (postcards), China (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Great Wall (postcards), China 1978 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Great Wall (postcards), China (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Guangzhou: The Chen Clan Academy (postcards), China (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Hangzhou (postcards), China (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Hong Kong (map), China (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Hong Kong (pamphlet) (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Kwangchow (pamphlet), China 1977 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Lintong (postcards), China (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Relics unearthed at Mawangdui (postcards), China (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Nanjing Cultural University (postcards), China (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Nanking (postcards), China (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Historical and scenic spots in Nanking, China (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Peking tourist pictures (leaflet collection), China (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Peking street guide, China (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Peking street guide: Peking, China 1978 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Shanghai (postcards), China (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Wousi (booklet), China (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Wuxi (postcards), China (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Singapore (postcards), China (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Official guide Singapore, China (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Singapore official guide, China (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Nuclear Power Plant, China (pamphlet) (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Ticket in Commemoration of Visit of Tian Anmen Gate (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Tian Anmen Gate (pamphlet) (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Zhong Shan Hot Spring Resort (pamphlet) (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Linxian (pamphlet) (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Nanjing Tourist Map 1985 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - The Great Wall (flyer) (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Transport Lines in Beijing City Area (map) (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Beijing (two flyers) 1988 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - The Chinese Research Academy of Environmental Sciences (flyer) 1980s (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Cavtat-Dubrovnik (hotel menu), Croatia (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Cruises: l'Atlantique, French Line (Box 5, Folder 19A)
  - Cruises: Around the World with Edwin C. Atkinson, Cunard Line (3 booklets) (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Cruises: Oxford QM2 Discovery Programme - Grand Maiden Voyage, Cunard Line (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Cruises: one book of passage certificates from the "Anchor" Line (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Treasures of: Copenhagen, Denmark (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Tourist guide: Three days in Quito, Ecuador (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Bienvenido a Quito (Ecuador [map]) (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Zona central de la ciudad de Quito (Ecuador [map]) 1973 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Principle Monuments: Cairo, Egypt (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Waterways: Entire, England (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Guide: Entire, England (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Guide: Osterly Park, England (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Illustrated Guide: Chastleton House, England (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Charlecote Park: Warwickshire, England (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Official Guide: Buckingham, England (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - In Brief: Cambridge, England (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Polsden Lacey: Surry, England (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Knole: Kent, England (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Historic York: York, England (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Zoo Park: Woburn, England (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Frank Tourist Tours: Entire, England (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Bone Cavern: Brixham, England (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Info: Kent, England (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Hardwick Hall: Derbyshire, England (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Langdale Pikes: Lakes, England (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Houses and Gardens: Entire, England (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Compton in the Hole: Compton Wynyates, England (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Brochure: Oxford, England (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Pamphlet: Brief Guide to Inn Signs (England) (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Pamphlet: More About Inn Signs (England) (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Kenilworth: Castles + Palaces, England (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Broughton: Castles + Palaces, England (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Hampton: Castles + Palaces, England (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Warwick: Castles + Palaces, England (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Durham: Castles + Palaces, England (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Dartmouth: Castles + Palaces, England (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Durham: Castles + Palaces, England (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Belvoir: Castles + Palaces, England (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Wilton House: Castles + Palaces, England (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Haddon Hall: Castles + Palaces, England (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Hampton Court: Castles + Palaces, England (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Houseteads Roman Fort: Castles + Palaces, England (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Stirling: Castles + Palaces, England (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Windsor: Castles + Palaces, England (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Howard: Castles + Palaces, England (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Cathedral Route of Great Britain: Cathedrals, England (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - St. Paul's: Cathedrals, England (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Lincoln: Cathedrals, England (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Durham: Cathedrals, England (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Canterbury: Cathedrals, England (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Winchester: Cathedrals, England (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Cambridge Holy Sepulchre Church: Chapel + Abbeys, England (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Woburn: Chapel + Abbeys, England (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Windsor, St. George's: Chapel + Abbeys, England (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stoneleigh: Chapel + Abbeys, England (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Westminster: Chapel + Abbeys, England (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Coronoation Church: Chapel + Abbeys, England (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - St. George's Chapel: Chapel + Abbeys, England (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - WoburnWoburn: Chapel + Abbeys, England (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Alban: Chapel + Abbeys, England (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Map + Route List: London, England (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Plan Guide: London, England (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Bacon's Road Map: London, England (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Map: London, England (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Street Plan: London, England (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Gardens and Parks: London, England (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Madame Tussaud's: London, England (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Zoo Guide: London, England (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - National Gallery: London, England (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Map: London, England (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - The Trafalgar (advertisement): London, England (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Six Historical Pictures In The Houses of Parliament [London, England] (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Authorised Guide: Tower of London, England (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Beauchamp Tower: Tower of London, England (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Beauchamp Tower: Tower of London, England (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Authorised Guide: Tower of London, England (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Day Tours: Tower of London, England (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Post Card: Tower of London, England (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Official Guide Book: Tower of London, England (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - The Crown Jewels: Tower of London, England (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Maps: North East, England (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Maps: North West, England (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Maps: Entire, England (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Maps: Entire, England (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Maps: Entire, England (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Maps: South West, England (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Maps: Northumberland/ Durham/ Yorkshire, England (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Maps: South/ South East, England (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Maps: Lakeland, England (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Maps: East Anglia, England (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Maps: Wales, England (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Maps: Herts/ Bucks, England (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Maps: Dartmoor, England (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Maps: London, England (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Official Guide: Stratford upon Avon, England (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Official Guide, 1957: Stratford upon Avon, England (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Story of Shakespeare: Stratford upon Avon, England (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - The Mentor: Shakespeare's Country, 1914, 1916: Stratford upon Avon, England (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 1969: General Map, Europe (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 1977: Celtic Map or Europe, Europe (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Crystal Cruises Europe 2004 (advertisement) (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Reynolds Continental Collections (European sweater patterns) (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - leaflet: Tourist information, Helsinki, Finland (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - guide: Helsinki/Helsingfors, Finland (Box 6, Folder 7)